

Ms. Thinzar Soe

CONTACT



thinzar9soe@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/thi nzar-soe

No. (66/72), Htee Dan Housing,



Kannar Road, Kyee Myin Dine Tsp, Yangon, Myanmar.

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Date of Birth : 9th February 1996

Passport No : MH 137182

Nationality : Myanmar

Gender : Female

Marital Status : Single

Expected Salary: SGD4000

SKILLS

Professional Abilities

- Time Management
- Responsibility
- Eager to learn
- Hard Work
- **Optimistic**
- Critical Thinking
- Collaboration
- Communication

Languages

- English (Communication)
- Chinese (Communication)
- Japanese (N3)
- Burmese (Native)
- Mon (Native)

ABOUT

I am working as a Web Developer for 5 years in Software Engineering industry. To build career in a growing organization, where I can get the opportunities to improve my abilities by accepting challenges, fulfilling the organizational goal and climb the career ladder through continuous learning and commitment.

WORK EXPERIENCES

Web Developer

August 2018 - Present

Kobebussan Myanmar Sule Square, Yangon

- Installing Apache, phpMyAdmin, PHP and MySQL
- Writing and debugging code
- Delivering project document by project manager
- Analyzing project requirement
- Discussing about a project requirement with team leader and project manager
- Joining requirement gathering meeting, trainings
- Testing finished project
- Testing user interface of developed for various views such as mobile view, tablet, desktop view, etc.
- Preparing developer documentations such as ER diagram, table structure, workflow, etc.
- Preparing user manual documentations
- Following to the code written by others when old projects needed to develop or to fix bug
- Designing T-Shirt for office trip
- Preparing database for user testing such as setting up database, importing
- During the covid period, work from home via remote
- Developing at least 30 projects

Internship

April 2018 - June 2018

Next Code Software Co., Ltd 30th Street, Yangon

- Updating window 10 and Visual Studio Code
- Installing Microsoft SQL, Angular JS, Ionic, Postman and Git Hub
- Using Trello and Bit Bucket.
- Learning Core UI, Demo and Bootstrap
- Researching and importing data to the client's database
- Going to the client's site.

EDUCATION BACKGROUND

Academic

West Yangon Technological University (W.Y.T.U)

- BTech.IT (Bachelor of Technology, Information Technology) | January 2017
- BE.IT (Bachelor of Engineer, Information Technology) | February 2019

Trainings and Certifications

Myanmar World Wide Web Institute (M3Wi)

- Web Essentials | May 2017
- PHP Web Developer | May 2018

GESC Chinese Language Training Centre

- Level I Course | March 2015
- Level II Chinese Speaking Course | May 2016

Wisdom for Life Child Protection Service

Communication Skills Training | July 2018

Japanese-Language Proficiency

- N4 | August 2019
- N3 | March 2023

SheCodes Foundation

(https://www.shecodes.io/graduates/ 73789-thinzar-soe)

- Introduction to Coding | March 2023
- Web Development | April 2023
- Responsive Web Development | May 2023
- React Development | May 2023

MANAWRAMA Gratis Monastery Educational Institute

A+ Hardware Course | December 2014

Success Language Academy

English Communication | July 2017

Part Time

Promotor | 18.03.2018 - 01.04.2018

- Working as a coffee promotor in Square Myanmar
- Serving customer in special events
- Inviting new customer for fun
- Rewarding for winner

Page Admin, Match Maker, Online friend, Online consultant | 2022 –2023

- Replying and making appointment as a page admin in Blind Date for You Consulting Agency
- Matching the boy customer and the girl customer as a match maker
- Talking and listening to customer who are in trauma or tired as an online friend
- Joining requirement gathering meeting and trainings for online consultant
- Listening and Advice to the customer as an online consultant.

Educational Guider

Computer Basic, Coding for Kid | 2022 - 2023

- Teaching at least 15 students for Computer Basic and Coding for Kid
- Including Microsoft Word, Microsoft Excel, Microsoft PowerPoint, typing both English and Burmese, computer organization, computer fundamental, Zoom, Gmail, Chrome, basic adobe photoshop and google, etc. in computer basic course
- Including 25 projects with scratch app and programming concept with code.org. Each level had challenges and assignment in coding for kid course

Mathematics | 2022 - 2023

- Teaching at least 11 students for Grade 9 and Grade 10
- Myanmar Government School Curriculum for Mathematics subject

Chinese Speaking Course | 2019 – 2020

- Searching the content for speaking
- Practicing with the student together

Volunteer

- Flood Disaster Event | 05.08.2015
- White Human Friendship Donation Group | 12.05.2018
- RecyGlo Myanmar | 27.06.2018
- Wisdom for Life Child Protection Service | 2017 2018

Work Related Skills

- HTML 5, CSS 3, Bootstrap, Flexbox, Wireframes, XML
- PHP, Python, Apache, Laravel, Xampp
- MySQL, Microsoft SQL, Data Structure
- JavaScript, JQuery, AJax, JSON, Axios, Angular JS, React JS
- Photoshop CS 6, Flash, Dreamweaver CS 6, Scratch, CODE.org
- Microsoft Word, Microsoft Excel, Microsoft PowerPoint, Page Maker
- Git Hub, Netlify, API, SEO